[{"answer": "I wouldn't call it white smoke yet but we're definitely at the point where we could at least look up to the tower and see if there could be smoke anytime soon, which is a lot further away than we were just a few hours ago, Piers.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Dana are we seeing a puff of political white smoke?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Did you clash with the President is that fair to say?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "If you focus on things that might be clashing, those are probably be in a book someday.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "How did you - What did you clash over, was it about how to reopen the government and went to do it?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I think that is a good sign, Piers.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "I hear that Joe Biden is still trapped inside the White House is that a good sign the great deal maker hasn't emerged yet?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, I'm encouraged.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Let's start with you Jim Himes, what are you sensing?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Well I agree very much actually with what Jim had to say.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "How do you see the deal which is probably pretty close to being done now actually being completed?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I never sort about looked to Donald Trump for what is true and good in this world, but also look, Donald Trump in his business when he doesn't like how something is going, he can just do as he does and say you're fired.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Have you got anything to say that this doesn't look very good the way this is all played out?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Tom Cole, do you think that Donald Trump is a force of evil in this world as Mr. Himes seemed to be implying at?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Hold it let me answer you a question.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "From the default?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Well that's a good question and I would still say if.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Now look, you are the man to talk to you here, where is this deal in the devil of the detail going to get done do you think?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Yes, you just had a great conversation with a Democrat and a Republican.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Is that your take on it?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "(inaudible) stuff, John King, thank you very much indeed.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "The question is how high of a political price did they pay to get them?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Well, going back to my experience on the Watergate Committee which you referenced.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "What is your take with all your experience at this?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "It started actually, my recollection is subsequent to the Nixon effort which ended up the way it ended up with his resignation.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Have you ever known Washington be so partisan vicious frankly, is this how'd become?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Well, my position with my client is that he committed no crime.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Now, your client has been charged of reckless driving and unlawful imprisonment, what is your position with him?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Well, he's on a motorcycle, you got to understand he's not in a motor vehicle where, you know, you're looking at your side mirrors and you feel a little bit more comfortable, safer.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Why is he looking behind him to make a lane change?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Well, with all (ph), obviously, I'm not defending or speaking to Benjamin's client where he is, but from a video standpoint, you know, I just don't buy it, I mean, he wasn't making a lane change.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What do you make of this defense of Mr. Cruz?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "They were surrounding that vehicle obviously -- look, don't forget this has been precipitated by 200 911 calls that these guys are riding, terrorizing the West Side Highway in Manhattan, one of the busiest streets in the country in that sort of pot-like (ph) mentality surrounding vehicles that got in their way and that's exactly what they did here and what I believe Mr. Cruz was doing was basically going to slow this guy down and basically surround these guys which they eventually did.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "What do you think he's doing?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Now is your proper defense is there is clearly, in my opinion, no wrong turn, this is a tragedy what we're seeing here but what I'll say is this, the law is if you reasonably believe that he was in danger when he acted then he is good to go.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "He raised -- and we've all seen the video, but do you think that there is a proper defense for what he did?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "You'll think of the family?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I have children.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "ORGAN: Wife, children?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Well, unfortunately the doctors have told him that he has 99 percent probability of never being able to walk again.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "First of all, what is his condition today?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, probably a lot but they really have to learn to get along.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Donald Trump, if you were the CEO of Washington Incorporated right now, how many times would you been saying, \"You're fired\" in the last few weeks?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Well, nobody knows.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "As a top businessman, what do you think of that?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Can you even believe that figure?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "They have played us.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "The laugh of the (inaudible) because actually they have a position of strength don't they?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Well, I thought it was one of the most outrageous things I've ever heard and I've been doing this for a quite a while.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "How did you feel when you heard the death payments to the widows and families of dead servicemen and women in the American military were not going to be paid?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "How these guys can get together and do better business?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Well, I think one of the biggest problem is that they don't like each other.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "What advice can you give about the arts of doing a deal, of doing business?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "I think it is, because I don't think he's a natural dealmaker.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Is that a problem, do you think?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Well, I do look.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "You go along with that?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Well, and again, it's jobs.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What do you do about it?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Yes ...", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "How do you feel as an American?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Well, you know, when the Statue of Liberty, Piers, was closed and they announced and everything, I thought it was very bad.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "As an American, do you not feel embarrassed when this kind of thing happens?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Donald, I like just to give an immediate reaction to all the following names with your apprentice, (inaudible), if they were in the board room, what you would say?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "OH, I'd hire, absolutely.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Hired or fired?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Well, I'd hire him.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Would you hire him?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "ObamaCare is a disaster.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "ObamaCare?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "I don't know if I can't do it like her.", "docId": "131010pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Has she taught you how to twerk?", "qSentId": 637}]